NNP	_	3	com	_	B-PERSON
NNP	_	3	com	_	I-PERSON
NNP	_	15	obj	17:nsbj;24:nsbj	L-PERSON
,	_	3	p	_	O
NN	_	3	appo	_	O
IN	_	10	case	_	O
NNP	_	10	com	_	B-ORG
NNP	_	10	com	_	I-ORG
NNP	_	10	com	_	I-ORG
NNP	_	5	ppmod	_	L-ORG
,	_	10	p	_	O
NNP	sem=loc	10	advnp	_	U-PERSON
,	_	3	p	_	O
VBD	_	15	aux	_	O
VBN	_	0	root	_	O
DT	_	17	det	_	O
NN	sem=clr	15	comp	_	O
IN	_	22	case	_	O
DT	_	22	det	_	O
NN	_	21	advnp	_	O
VBG	_	22	attr	_	O
NN	_	17	ppmod	_	O
,	_	15	p	_	O
VBG	_	15	advcl	_	O
DT	_	26	det	_	O
NN	_	24	obj	_	O
.	_	15	p	_	O

